Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiocassettes, 1980 -- 1999; 1993 -- 1998; MS074.003; 2.2 Linear Feet; 17 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Chuck Colson, Christians' vital role in government, 1995; MS074.003.012.00036 (Box 12)
    IFAS tape 306 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Judge Robert Bork, Examining our modern-day scales of justice, 1995; MS074.003.012.00037 (Box 12)
    IFAS tape 307 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Lamar Alexander, Walking a steady pace for America's future, 1995; MS074.003.012.00038 (Box 12)
    IFAS tape 308 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Lt. Gov. Mike Huckabee, A grassroots success story, 1995; MS074.003.012.00039 (Box 12)
    IFAS tape 309 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Peter Marshall, The necessity of moral leadership, 1995; MS074.003.012.00040 (Box 12)
  - Weyrich, Jackson, Williams - Moderated by Mona Charen, Talking back to America, 1995; MS074.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 310 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Dr. Alan Keyes, Returning to moral stability, 1995; MS074.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 311 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Ralph Reed, Contract with the American family, 1995; MS074.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 312. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Honorable Chris Smith, U.N.'s Beijing Conference - A new global feminism, 1995; MS074.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 314 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Gribbin/Cheney/D'Sousa, Political correctness - stranglehold on our universities, 1995; MS074.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 315 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Fournier/Hudson/Flaherty/Melady, Forming a Catholic-evangelical coalition, 1995; MS074.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 316 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Patterson/Gonzalez/Sanchez/Molina/Fernandez, Strengthening partnerships with the Hispanic community, 1995; MS074.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 317 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Salce/Weinhold/Cooper/Mitchell, Coalition building, 1995; MS074.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 318 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Cunningham/Grey/Kindt/Kincaid, Gambling - rolling the dice on America's future, 1995; MS074.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 319 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Brown/Berry/Plummer/Hunt, Expanding the pro-family movement into the Black community, 1995; MS074.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 320 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Steve Moore & Scott Hodge, The budget deficit - a moral crisis for America, 1995; MS074.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 321 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Jay Sekulow, Freedom of religious expression, 1995; MS074.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 322 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Stirrup/Gordon/Marzulla/Lewis, Landowners' vanishing rights, 1995; MS074.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 323 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Green/Moore/Rosenberger, Faith in the public square, 1995; MS074.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 324 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Welch/Johnson/Dannenfelfer, Victories for the unborn, 1995; MS074.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 325 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - D. Gribbin/R. Combs, Christian Coalition chapter briefing, 1995; MS074.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 326 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Dilley/Bell/Smith, Parental rights, 1995; MS074.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 327 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Simmons/Foster/Holland/Manno, Elementary school curriculum - are we dumbing down America, 1995; MS074.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 328 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - C. Parks/D. Lopin, Moderator, Influencing Federal legislation, 1995; MS074.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 329 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Faulkner/Overgard/Weddington, The church's civic duty, 1995; MS074.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 330 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Hardman/Ferrara/Bailey, Medicare crisis, 1995; MS074.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 331 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - J. Dowless/C. Halford, Building a neighborhood organization, 1995; MS074.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 332 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - P. Trueman/L. Sheldon, Pornography - robbing our children of innocence, 1995; MS074.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 333 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Russell/Riggs/Parker/Jordan, School choice - the next victory, 1995; MS074.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 334 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Paul Weyrich, Rights and wrongs of the religious right, 1995; MS074.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 336. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Whittmann/Tate/Weinstein/Boehm, Defending advocacy groups, 1995; MS074.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 337. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Calligan, Fund, Luntz, The 104th Congress - A new vision for America, 1995; MS074.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 338. From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Campbell/Furlow/Hirschmann, Preserving the pro-life plank, 1995; MS074.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 339 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Baran/Mitchell/Bloomfield, Fundamental tax reform, 1995; MS074.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 340 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Naylor/Hadley/Donnelly, Military in Clinton years, 1995; MS074.003.013.00030 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 34 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Spilde/Smith/Tiahrt, New issues in Congress, 1995; MS074.003.013.00031 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 342 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - E.V. Hill, Gala banquet, 1995; MS074.003.013.00032 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 343 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Oliver North, Gala banquet, 1995; MS074.003.013.00033 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 344 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Pat Buchanan, Gala banquet, 1995; MS074.003.013.00034 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 345 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Steve Fry, Worship service, 1995; MS074.003.013.00035 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 346 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Patti D'Angelo, Guest singer, 1995; MS074.003.013.00036 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 347 (number from index). From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1995.
  - Dr. Stanley Monteith, 1995; MS074.003.013.00037 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 348. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Workshop issues panel, 1995; MS074.003.013.00038 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 349. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Sheri Rose Shepherd, Mrs. USA, Rep. Linda Smith, 1995; MS074.003.013.00039 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 350. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Pastor David Moore, 1995; MS074.003.013.00040 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 351. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Winning as a religious conservative, Shelly A. Uscinski, 1995; MS074.003.013.00041 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 352. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Developing your campaign plan & message, Mark P. Campbell, MS074.003.013.00042 (Box 13)
    IFAS tape 353. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Targeting voters & building coalitions, Tim Phillips, MS074.003.014.00001 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 354. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Dealing with teachers unions, David Y. Denholm, MS074.003.014.00002 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 355. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Education reform & school choice, David W. Kirkpatrick, MS074.003.014.00003 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 356. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Building an effective grassroots organization, Mark P. Campbell, MS074.003.014.00004 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 357. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Academic standards and Outcome-Based Education, Dr. Chester E. Finn, Jr., MS074.003.014.00005 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 358. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - Developing & implementing a fund-raising plan, Tim Phillips, MS074.003.014.00006 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 359. A Christian Coalition School Board Training Seminar tape.
  - "Pornography on the Internet," Pat Trueman, 1995; MS074.003.014.00007 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 361. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Pat Buchanan, 1995; MS074.003.014.00008 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 363. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Senator Robert Dole, 1995; MS074.003.014.00009 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 364. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "An alternative to public education," Debbie Beyer, 1995; MS074.003.014.00010 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 365. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Dr. Tim Lee, 1995; MS074.003.014.00011 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 366. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Elaine Donnelly, 1995; MS074.003.014.00012 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 367. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Mary Beth Bonacci, 1995; MS074.003.014.00013 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 368. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "Preparing teens for the world in the classroom," Christine O'Donnell - Kenda Bartlett, 1995; MS074.003.014.00014 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 369. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Senator Phil Gramm, 1995; MS074.003.014.00015 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 370. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "Homosexuality in America's mainstream," Jim Woodall - Col. Ron Ray - Dr. Judith Reisman, 1995; MS074.003.014.00016 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 371. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Dr. Ralph Reed, 1995; MS074.003.014.00017 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 372. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "Can we stop funding the liberal left?" Howard Phillips, 1995; MS074.003.014.00018 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 373. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "Parental rights are still right," Douglas Phillips, JD, 1995; MS074.003.014.00019 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 374. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Rep. Sam Johnson, 1995; MS074.003.014.00020 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 375. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Congressional issues panel, Rep. L. Smith, Rep. E. Istook, Rep. S. Stockman, 1995; MS074.003.014.00021 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 376. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Rep. Bob Dornan, 1995; MS074.003.014.00022 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 377. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "Outcome-Based Education," Pamela Hobb Hoffecker, Peg Luksik, 1995; MS074.003.014.00023 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 378. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "CWA leadership opportunities in your area," Kimberley Slye, 1995; MS074.003.014.00024 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 379. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - "The life of the party," Morton Blackwell, 1995; MS074.003.014.00025 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 380. From Concerned Women for America Convention, 1995.
  - Intellectual bridges the evolutionist must cross, Adrian Rogers, MS074.003.014.00026 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 381. "A message by Bill Elliff pastor of 1st Bapt. Church Little Rock."
  - Leviticus XIX Lines 11, 12, 13, MS074.003.014.00027 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 382
  - Carl Klang, Watch out for martial law, 194, 1994; MS074.003.014.00028 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 383.
  - The Latter-Day Saints, Profile of a covenant people, 1995; MS074.003.014.00029 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 384.
  - FOF Atty's Conf. Steve McFarland, Defending victims of political correctness on campus, 1995-03-01 -- 1995-03-05; MS074.003.014.00030 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 385
  - Sntr. Phil Gramm RTV, How D.C. can win Americas trust, 1995; MS074.003.014.00031 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 386
  - [Side A] Rabbi Lapin 1995 RTV, Jewish & Xtian unity; [Side B] Cooper v. Aaron Heart of Atlanta Motel v. US, MS074.003.014.00032 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 387
  - Pat Buchanan, RTV V, 1995; MS074.003.014.00033 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 388
  - Alternative radio, "The Christian right," Chip Berlet (Political Research Associates), 1995-09-05; MS074.003.014.00034 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 391
  - Secrets of the homosexual movement, Paul Mero / Secrets of a career politician, Huck Walther, MS074.003.014.00035 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 394 (tape 1). Originally housed in a vinyl case with title "Secrets of Washington, Restore America home lobbyist kit." From Christian Action Network.
  - The secrets of the feminist movement, Ruth Pakaluk / The shameful truth Bill & Hillary don't want you to know, Floyd Brown, MS074.003.014.00036 (Box 14)
    IFAS tape 394 (tape 2). Originally housed in a vinyl case, with title "Secrets of Washington, Restore America home lobbyist kit." From Christian Action Network.
  - Newt Gingrich, "The Window of Opportunity", 1985; MS074.003.014.00037 (Box 14)
    From American Coalition for Traditional Values, "How to Win an Election" conference, October, 1985.
  - Theocracy in America? The religious right's political agenda, Debate with Skipp Porteous and the Rev. Louis Sheldon, MS074.003.014.00038 (Box 14)
    From Americans United for Separation of Church and State, 46th National Conference on Church and State
  - "Fighting crime: liberal panaceas, conservative solution," speaker: Richard Sellers, 1994; MS074.003.014.00039 (Box 14)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1994.
  - Appell/Jackson/Richardson, Communicating the pro-family message, 1995; MS074.003.014.00040 (Box 14)
    From the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory Conference, 1995.
  - Strengthen families by reducing government, Representative Dick Armey, 1996; MS074.003.014.00041 (Box 14)
    From the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1996.
  - Reviving our moral strength, Senator John Ashcroft, 1996; MS074.003.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Politics, technology & the 21st. century, Baran, West, Ballard, 1996; MS074.003.015.00002 (Box 15)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1996
  - America's Godly heritage, David Barton, 1996; MS074.003.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Culture, character, and politics - Dr. Bill Bennett, 1996; MS074.003.015.00004 (Box 15)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1996.
  - America's best days are ahead - Pat Buchanan, 1996; MS074.003.015.00005 (Box 15)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory Conference, 1996.
  - Adoption and child welfare, Clark, Fagan, Pierce, Craig, 1996; MS074.003.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - How faith & compassion can make America strong, Senator Dan Coats, 1996; MS074.003.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Charting a course for a pro-family Congress, Rep. Tom Delay, 1996; MS074.003.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - A spiritual rebirth of our inner cities, DeLeon, Woodson, 1996; MS074.003.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - America's bright prospects in the new millennium, Bob Dole & Jack Kemp, 1996; MS074.003.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Faith, freedom and family, Representative Bob Dornan, 1996; MS074.003.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Today's tips for effective lobbying, Dowless, Lopina, Cunningham, 1996; MS074.003.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Today's tips for effective lobbying, Dowless, Lopina, Cunningham [tape 2], 1996; MS074.003.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Strengthening our Jewish & Christian values, Rabbi Yechiel Eckstein, 1996; MS074.003.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Eliminating the IRS as we know it, Fellendorf, Mitchell, Norquist, Moore, 1996; MS074.003.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Preserving parental rights, Fisher, Bell, May, Tucker, 1996; MS074.003.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Realizing the American dream, Newt Gingrich, 1996; MS074.003.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - International war on Christianity, Grabinski, Horowitz, Knippers, Cizik, 1996; MS074.003.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Building grassroots organization from precinct level, Gribbin, Calligan, 1996; MS074.003.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Preserving traditional values, Senator Jesse Helms, 1996; MS074.003.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Gala banquet, Governor Mike Huckabee, 1996; MS074.003.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Racial reconciliation: rising from the ashes, Jackson, Freeman, Haygood, Mahoney, 1996; MS074.003.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Talking back to America, Jackson, Williams, Charen, Weyrich, 1996; MS074.003.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Welfare reform, Karrer, Rector, Parker, Haskins, 1996; MS074.003.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Pundits and polling, Keen, Fund, Fitzpatrick, 1996; MS074.003.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - America's yearning for spiritual renewal, Alan Keyes, 1996; MS074.003.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Cherishing our Judeo-Christian heritage, Rabbie Daniel Lapin, 1996; MS074.003.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - American renewal, Reverend Peter Marshall, 1996; MS074.003.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - New strategies on protecting the unborn, McCormack, Johnson, Jefferson, Canady, 1996; MS074.003.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Rescuing our property rights, McCormack, Eidsmoe, Gordon, 1996; MS074.003.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Duty, honor and country, Oliver North, 1996; MS074.003.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Organizing a multi-racial coalition, Olmi, Jackson, Ellis, Myers, 1996; MS074.003.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Hope for a new generation, Star Parker, 1996; MS074.003.015.00033 (Box 15)
  - The Granite Foundation, Ross Perot, 1996; MS074.003.015.00034 (Box 15)
  - Vouchers & tax credits - time for parents to choose, Quinn, Reilly, Bolick, Robinson, 1996; MS074.003.015.00035 (Box 15)
  - Vouchers & tax credits - time for parents to choose, Quinn, Reilly, Bolick, Robinson [tape 2], 1996; MS074.003.015.00036 (Box 15)
  - Pat Robertson, Introduction, 1996; MS074.003.015.00037 (Box 15)
  - Active faith, Dr. Ralph E. Reed, Jr., 1996; MS074.003.015.00038 (Box 15)
  - Pat Robertson, Keynote address, 1996; MS074.003.015.00039 (Box 15)
  - Forging a Catholic-evangelical alliance, Roselli, Fournier, Neuhaus, 1996; MS074.003.015.00040 (Box 15)
  - Forming a Catholic-evangelical coalition, Roselli, Fournier, Bell, Tiboni, Hudson, Lettieri, 1996; MS074.003.015.00041 (Box 15)
  - Standing for life, Phyllis Schlafly, 1996; MS074.003.015.00042 (Box 15)
  - Liberty and justice for all, Jay Sekulow, 1996; MS074.003.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - New Israeli politics, Spilde, Levens, Hellman, Wihbey, 1996; MS074.003.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Moral leadership - foundation for America's renewal, Representative J.C. Watts, 1996; MS074.003.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Gambling - Welch, Grey, Kincaid, Barbee, Wolf, 1996; MS074.003.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Activism on the Internet, 1996; MS074.003.016.00005 (Box 16)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conference, 1998
  - Advancing the cause of life, 1998; MS074.003.016.00006 (Box 16)
    From Christian Coalition's Road to Victory Conference, 1998
  - Rep. Dick Armey, Majority Leader - U.S. House of Representatives, 1998; MS074.003.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Sen. John Ashcroft, U.S. Senate, 1998; MS074.003.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Hon. Gary Bauer, President - Family Research Council, 1998; MS074.003.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Bill Bright - President, Campus Crusade for Christ, 1998; MS074.003.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Chapter leader briefing, 1998; MS074.003.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Hon. Linda Chavez, President - Center for Equal Opportunity, 1998; MS074.003.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Hon. Chuck Colson - Chairman, Prison Fellowship, 1998; MS074.003.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Creating a family-friendly tax code, 1998; MS074.003.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Rep. Tom Delay, Majority Whip - U.S. House of Representatives, 1998; MS074.003.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Effective involvement in a political party, 1998; MS074.003.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Effectively communicating our message, 1998; MS074.003.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Fighting religious persecution abroad, 1998; MS074.003.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Steve Forbes, President - Forbes Magazine, 1998; MS074.003.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Rep. Newt Gingrich, Speaker - U.S. House of Representatives, 1998; MS074.003.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Is the media biased?, 1998; MS074.003.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Hon. Kay Coles James, Dean, Robertson School of Government, Regent Univ, 1998; MS074.003.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Rep. John Kasich, U.S. House of Representatives, 1998; MS074.003.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Ambassador Alan Keyes, "The Alan Keyes Show - America's wake-up call", 1998; MS074.003.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Rabbi Daniel Lapin, President - Toward tradition, 1998; MS074.003.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Sen. Trent Lott, Majority Leader - U.S. Senate, 1998; MS074.003.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Sen. Mitch McConnell, U.S. Senate, 1998; MS074.003.016.00027 (Box 16)
  - Lt. Col. Oliver North, USMC (Ret.) - "The Oliver North Show", 1998; MS074.003.016.00028 (Box 16)
  - Our Godly hertiage [sic] and civic duty, 1998; MS074.003.016.00029 (Box 16)
  - Passing the Religious Freedom Amendment, 1998; MS074.003.016.00030 (Box 16)
  - Pornography - assault on women and children, 1998; MS074.003.016.00031 (Box 16)
  - Promoting traditional marriage, 1998; MS074.003.016.00032 (Box 16)
  - Property rights and Christian stewardship of our natural resources, 1998; MS074.003.016.00033 (Box 16)
  - Hon. Dan Quayle, former Vice President of the United States, 1998; MS074.003.016.00034 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Ralph Reed, Jr., President - Century Strategies, 1998; MS074.003.016.00035 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Pat Robertson, Founder and Chairman - Christian Coalition, 1998; MS074.003.016.00036 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Pat Robertson - II, Founder & Chairman - Christian Coalition, 1998; MS074.003.016.00037 (Box 16)
  - Phyllis Schlafly, President - Eagle Forum, 1998; MS074.003.016.00038 (Box 16)
  - Jay Sekulow, Chief Counsel - American Center for Law and Justice, 1998; MS074.003.016.00039 (Box 16)
  - Sen. Bob Smith, U.S. Senate, 1998; MS074.003.016.00040 (Box 16)
  - Rep. Randy Tate, Executive Director - Christian Coalition, 1998; MS074.003.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - The Tyranny of judicial activism, 1998; MS074.003.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Rep. J.C. Watts, U.S. House of Representatives, 1998; MS074.003.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Worship service - Bishop Earl Jackson, 1998; MS074.003.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Zig Ziglar, President - The Zig Ziglar Foundation, 1998; MS074.003.017.00005 (Box 17)